you.
The lights are dimming in the hall, the shadows
climbing up the wall. We check the dials, turn
the wheel, but there is nothing left to feel. The
engine shudders, then I stops. The pressure in
the chamber drops. It's just a fading spark, a
flicker in the growing dark. We're running out
of time and space Inside this hollow, empty
place The Fading Spot
You search the wiring for a sign, you trace the
path of every line. The system crashes one by one
until the work is left undone. We build a
fortress way too high, and watch the coal hours
bleed and die. It's just a fading spark. A
flicker in the growing dark We're running out of
time and space Inside this hollow, empty place
The fading spark
Is I over? Is I done? Waiting for the fadding sun
No one's left to play the part Hide the secret in
your heart
It's just a fading spark A flicker in the growing
dark We're running out of time and space Inside
this hollow, empty place The fading spark
Fade to grey. Fade to black. Fade to grey.